{
    "subject": "resource/Barry_Van_Dyke",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Barry Van Dyke was born in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9847090244293213,
            "question": "In the United States, where was Barry Van Dyke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9655642509460449,
            "question": "Was Barry Van Dyke born outside the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921111524105072,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke from the USA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8765645623207092,
            "question": "Where was Barry Van Dyke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.839627742767334,
            "question": "Is Barry Van Dyke American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7834198474884033,
            "question": "Where in the world was Barry Van Dyke born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7390835881233215,
            "question": "Barry Van Dyke's nationality is?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7037658095359802,
            "question": "What country is Barry Van Dyke's birthplace in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6958123445510864,
            "question": "What is Barry Van Dyke's place of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.450114905834198,
            "question": "What is Barry Van Dyke's origin country?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Barry Van Dyke was born in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1205_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Barry Van Dyke's place of birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1205_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Barry Van Dyke's birthplace in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1205_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Barry Van Dyke's nationality is?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1205_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1205_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Barry Van Dyke was born in Atlanta, Georgia, USA, which is a country in North America and part of the larger geographical region known as the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents consistently state that Barry Van Dyke was born on July 31, 1951, in Atlanta, Georgia, which is part of the United States. Therefore, the statement \"Barry Van Dyke was born in the United States\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}